 let questions = [
     {
         numb: 1,
         question: "What does HTML stand for?",
         answer: "Hypertext Markup Language",
         options:[
             "Hard To Make Love",
             "Hypertext Markup Language",
             "Hey That's My Lunch",
             "Hyper Tool Markup Language"
         ]
     },
     {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What is the biggest lie in computer programming?",
        answer: "HTML is a programming language",
        options:[
            "It should work now",
            "I solved a bug",
            "HTML is a programming language",
            "Oh it's gonna be easy"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What is the greatest fear of programmers ?",
        answer: "When they forget to save.",
        options:[
            "BUGs! BUGs! BUGs everywhere :/",
            "Deploy on Friday evening.",
            "When they forget to save.",
            "When test fails when run together but passes alone."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which is the most used language for web development?",
        answer: "JavaScript",
        options:[
            "JavaScript",
            "Human language",
            "Java",
            "HTML"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Oct 31 = Dec 25 ?",
        answer: "Octal 31 is equel to Decimal 25",
        options:[
            "Halloween = Christmas",
            "Octal 31 is equel to Decimal 25",
            "Not equal",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "What is a web developer's favorite snack?",
        answer: "Cookies",
        options:[
            "Chocolate",
            "Coffee",
            "All the snacks",
            "Cookies"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What does SEO stand for?",
        answer: "Search Engine Optimization",
        options:[
            "Sure Enjoy Optimizing",
            "Silence Everyones Opinion",
            "Search Engine Optimization",
            "Search Everything Online"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "IsNaN() Evaluates And Argument To Determine if Given Value:",
        answer: "Is Not a numb",
        options:[
            "Is Not a numb",
            "Is Not a Null",
            "Is Not a New Object",
            "Is Not a New"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What is a WTF?",
        answer: "Type of parent theme",
        options:[
            "Where's the Faith",
            "Walk To Freedom",
            "Type of parent theme",
            "Web Task Force"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What ia an API?",
        answer: "A software intermediary that allows two applications to talk to each other.",
        options:[
            "A software intermediary that allows two applications to talk to each other.",
            "A database",
            "A Framework",
            "An Application"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "What is ReactJS?",
        answer: "A Library for building interaction interfaces",
        options:[
            "User-interface framework",
            "Server-side Framework",
            "A Library for building interaction interfaces",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "What of the following API is a MUST for every ReactJS component?",
        answer: "renderComponent",
        options:[
            "renderComponent",
            "getInitialState",
            "render",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "What does the 'webpack' command do?",
        answer: "A module bundler",
        options:[
            "A module bundler",
            "Deliver free web pages",
            "Web pack collector",
            "Runs react local development server"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "What is GitHub?",
        answer: "a code hosting platform for version-control and collaboration platform",
        options:[
            "a code hosting platform for version-control and collaboration platform",
            "a social development environment for front-end designers",
            "a zero-setup, collaborative, browser-based coding editor",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question:"What is code hoisting?",
        answer: "All",
        options:[
            "the default behavior of moving all the declarations at the top of the scope before code execution.",
            "lift, raise",
            "JavaScript's default behavior of moving all declarations to the top of the current scope",
            "All"
        ]
    },
 ];